(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
昔々、あるところに
Once upon a time, in a certain place,
一人ぼっちのメイドがいました。
there was a lonely maid.
そのメイドは成績が悪く、人と話すことが苦手で、
The maid's grades were poor, she was bad at talking to people,
いつも俯いていました。
and always looked down.
周りと馴染むことができなかったメイドは、
Unable to fit in with those around her, the maid
いつしか部屋に引きこもるようになりました。
eventually became a shut-in.
いつものようにネットサーフィンをしていたある日、
One day, while surfing the net as usual,
一つの記事がメイドの目に留まりました。
an article caught the maid's eye.
この出会いがメイドの人生を大きく変えたのでした。
This encounter changed the maid's life forever.
これは一人ぼっちだった引きこもりのメイドが、
This is the story of a lonely, shut-in maid who,
出会った仲間と共に、銀河一のアイドルになるお話。
together with the friends she met, becomes the number one idol in the galaxy.
今日のおはよう 少しドキドキするな
Today's "good morning" is a little heart-pounding
きらきら
作詞・作曲 DECO*27
編曲 Rockwell
Kira Kira
Lyrics & Composition: DECO*27
Arrangement: Rockwell
選ばれるかって不安になって あぁ
Worrying if I'll be chosen, ah
ダメなところばかりで嫌になるな
Hating myself for all my flaws
進んでみたって上手くいかないけど
Even if I move forward, things don't go well
また大失敗は おなかいっぱい
Another big failure, I've had my fill
変わりたくて振り絞ったから
But I mustered my strength because I wanted to change
描いた未来を好きになりたいから
Because I want to like the future I envisioned
きらきらっと輝こうか
Let's shine brightly
間違えちゃっても大丈夫
It's okay if you make a mistake
できないことできるよになれるよ
You'll be able to do what you can't now
先は長いから
Because the road ahead is long
きらきら
Sparkle
疲れちゃったら止まろうか
Shall we stop if we get tired?
少し眠ったら元通り
After a little sleep, we'll be back to normal.
したいことしたいようにしなくちゃ
I have to do what I want to do the way I want.
あたしじゃないでしょう？
Or it wouldn't be me, right?
忘れないよこの思いは
I won't forget these feelings.
重ねてもっと届くように
I'll pile them up to reach you more.
変えられるんだ変えていくんだ
I can change, I will change.
きらきらしたいから
Because I want to sparkle.
nanana...
きらきらっと輝こうか
Shall we sparkle and shine?
間違えちゃっても大丈夫
It's okay to make mistakes.
できないことできるようになれるよ
You'll be able to do what you couldn't.
先は長いから
Because the road is long.
疲れちゃったら止まろうか
Shall we stop if we get tired?
少し眠ったら元通り
After a little sleep, we'll be back to normal.
したいことしたいようにしなくちゃ
I have to do what I want to do the way I want.
あたしじゃないでしょう？
Or it wouldn't be me, right?
忘れないよこの思いは
I won't forget these feelings.
重ねてもっと届くように
I'll pile them up to reach you more.
変えられるんだ変えていくんだ
I can change, I will change.
きらきらしたいから
Because I want to sparkle.
ダメなあたし ずっとずっと歌うよ
The useless me will sing forever and ever.
輝けること 変われちゃうこと
Being able to shine, being able to change.
ダメなあたし ずっとずっと見ていてほしい
I want you to watch the useless me forever.
あいわな
I Wanna
月曜日は体が動きません
On Mondays my body doesn't move.
ていうか毎日でした ピリピリ偏頭痛
Actually, it was every day. A stinging migraine.
あたしったらメイドのくせしてお料理ダメ
Me, a maid, but bad at cooking.
掃除もちょっとお粗末
And my cleaning is a bit sloppy.
てんてこ舞いで舞った 正真正銘の涙目です
Danced in a flurry. Truly teary-eyed.
へいゆー！ 会いたくなってしまったな 今夜も
Hey you! I've wanted to see you tonight too.
夜な夜な集まって何する？
What are we doing gathering night after night?
月火水木金土日 365日
Mon Tue Wed Thu Fri Sat Sun, 365 days.
画面越しご挨拶 せーの！
Greeting through the screen. Ready, go!
好きだっちゃ！て言っちゃったって 全然可愛くない
Saying "I like you!" isn't cute at all.
勝手にへこんだって 泣いてみたって 全然可愛くない
Feeling down or crying on my own, it's not cute at all.
君だって同じ ダメよりの人種です
You're the same. You're the useless type.
そんな優しくして... あたしに気があるのかな？
Being so kind... do you like me?
もうこんな時間 どんな予感 カミハプニング
Already this late. What a premonition. God-happening.
中毒症状 依存度マックス メンタル崩壊
Withdrawal, max dependence, mental breakdown.
あなたのことを もっともっと知りたい
I want to know more and more about you.
水曜日は意識がレボリューション
Wednesdays, consciousness is a revolution.
ていうか毎日でした ピリピリ偏頭痛
Actually, it was every day. A stinging migraine.
あたしったら競争社会不適合者
Me, a misfit in competitive society.
でも挙動は適合者
But behaving like a fit person.
のフリして暴言吐いて うん、へこんだ これって誇張事故？
Pretending, spitting abuse. Yeah, I'm down. Is this an exaggerated accident?
へいゆー！ 会いたくなってしまったな 今夜も
Hey you! I've wanted to see you tonight too.
自己嫌悪からの脱却
Escaping from self-loathing.
悪霊退散成敗 陰陽師さんなんとか...
Evil spirits banished. Onmyouji-san, do something...
頑張れあたし 負けるな！ せーの！
Do your best, me! Don't lose! Ready, go!
好きだっちゃ！て言っちゃったって 全然可愛くない
Saying "I like you!" isn't cute at all.
勝手にへこんだって 泣いてみたって 全然可愛くない
Feeling down or crying on my own, it's not cute at all.
君だって同じ ダメよりの人種です
You're the same. You're the useless type.
そんな優しくして... あたしに気があるのかな？
Being so kind... do you like me?
もうこんな時間 どんな予感 カミハプニング
Already this late. What a premonition. God-happening.
中毒症状 依存度マックス メンタル崩壊
Withdrawal, max dependence, mental breakdown.
あなたのことを もっともっと知りたい
I want to know more and more about you.
ああ 特別じゃない
Ah, I'm not special.
私のこと勘違いして...
You've misunderstood me...
馬鹿ね...
How silly...
なれあいこそが
Mutual dependency is what...
君と僕を繋ぐ光
Connects you and me, the light.
今日は来てくれてありがとう！
Thank you for coming today!
5周年ライブ、最後まで見てね！
It's my 5th Anniversary Live! Watch until the end!
月火水
Mon, Tue, Wed
木金土日 365日
Thu, Fri, Sat, Sun, 365 days
画面越しにご挨拶
Sending greetings through the screen
“こんあくあ〜”
“Kon Aqua!”
せーの！
One, two!
嫌いだって言ったって全然可愛くない
Even if you say you hate me, it's not cute at all
勝手に凹んじゃって泣いてみたって全然可愛くない
Getting depressed or crying on your own isn't cute either
君だって同じダメよりの人種です
You're the same kind of hopeless person as me
どんだけ優しくするの…？ 私のこと好きなの？
How kind are you going to be...? Do you like me?
確定！
Confirmed!
まどろむ時間
Slumbering time
どん欲な予感
A greedy premonition
神ハプニング
A god-tier occurrence
嗚呼中毒症状
Ah, these withdrawal symptoms
依存度はMax
The dependence is at Max
メンタル崩壊
Mental breakdown
あなたのことをもっともっと知りたい
I want to know more and more about you
まだあなたのことを何にも知らない
I still don't know anything about you yet
私のこと好きすぎ！
You like me way too much!
手が震えて冷たい。
My hands are shaking and cold.
足がすくむ。
My legs are trembling.
鼓動が速くなるのを感じる。
I can feel my heart beating faster.
緊張… か。
Nervousness... I guess.
もう5年もやってるのにな。
Even though I've been doing this for 5 years.
歓声が聞こえる。
I hear the cheers.
熱気が伝わってくる。
I can feel the heat from the crowd.
失敗したらどうしよう。
What if I fail?
満足してもらえなかったらどうしよう。
What if they aren't satisfied?
苦しい。
It's so tight.
大丈夫、大丈夫。
It's okay, it's okay.
いつも通り、平常心。
Just like always, stay calm.
みんなに届けたい。
I want to reach everyone.
5年分の感謝。
5 years' worth of gratitude.
伝われ、伝われ。
Let it reach them, please let it reach them.
ほら行くよ。
Hey, let's go.
最高の景色、一緒に見に行こう、あくたん！
Let's go see the best view together, Akutan!
…っ！
...!
うん。
Yeah.
今日はもう引き返そうかな
Maybe I should just turn back today
明日はもっと行けるかな
I wonder if I can go further tomorrow
見つけたい遠く 嬉しいを多く
I want to find lots of happiness far away
キラリ光る Hope
A sparkling Hope
動く 動く
Moving, moving
とりとめない Talk
Rambling talk
どこまでも続く
Continuing on forever
さよならさ孤独
Farewell, loneliness
we go walk,
動く 動く
moving, moving
難解なパズルを解く様に
Like solving a difficult puzzle
きっと何回も「知りたい」を知るから
Because we'll surely know the "want to know" many times
だから 1・2・3 で歩き出せ
So start walking on 1, 2, 3
今日も明日も昨日も変わらない
Today, tomorrow, and yesterday are the same
ならば 1・2・3 で歩き出せ
Then start walking on 1, 2, 3
回る世界と逆向きで
In the opposite direction of the spinning world
そうさ 1・2・3 で踊りだせ
That's right, start dancing on 1, 2, 3
今日も明日も昨日も忘れたい
Today, tomorrow, and yesterday, I want to forget it all
ならば 1・2・3 で動き出せ
Then start moving on 1, 2, 3
きっとそれが A A A Answer さ
Surely that is the Answer
巨大な灰色の壁
A huge grey wall
どうしたいかまだわからないから
Because I still don't know what I want to do
進む事のほか遠く
Besides moving forward, far away
けどいつか届く
but someday it will reach
その先が Goal
The path ahead is the Goal
動く 動く
Moving, moving
とどのつまり Joke
In the end, it's just a joke
それをきっと誇る
Surely we'll be proud of it
まだ少し行ける
We can still go a bit further
we go walk,
動く 動く
moving, moving
暖かいコーヒーすする様に
Like sipping warm coffee
ずっと待った甲斐それが今示すから
Because now it shows that it was worth the wait
だから 1・2・3 で笑い出せ
So start laughing on 1, 2, 3
今日も明日も昨日も変わらない
Today, tomorrow, and yesterday are the same
だけど 1・2・3 で笑い出せ
But start laughing on 1, 2, 3
変わる景色と同じ様に
Just like the changing scenery
そうさ 1・2・3 で踊りだせ
That's right, start dancing on 1, 2, 3
今日も明日も昨日も忘れたい
Today, tomorrow, and yesterday, I want to forget it all
ならば 1・2・3 で動き出せ
Then start moving on 1, 2, 3
きっとそれが A A A Answer さ
Surely that is the Answer
Dreamy day
今も難解な
Still, like solving...
パズルを解くように
...a complex puzzle.
何回も
Over and over again,
「知りたい」を知るから
because I've come to know "wanting to know".
だから
And so,
1・2・3で歩きだせ
start walking on 1, 2, 3.
今日も明日も昨日も変わらない
Today, tomorrow, and yesterday are the same.
ならば 1・2・3で歩きだせ
If so, start walking on 1, 2, 3.
回る世界と逆向きで
Against the turning of the world.
そろそろ 1・2・3で踊りだせ
It's time to start dancing on 1, 2, 3.
今日も明日も昨日も忘れたい
Today, tomorrow, and yesterday—I want to forget them.
ならば 1・2・3で動きだせ
If so, start moving on 1, 2, 3.
きっとそれが 心が
Surely that's what my heart...
求めた Answer
...has been searching for: the answer.
1・2・3で動きだせ
Start moving on 1, 2, 3.
おかゆ、今日はありがとね！
Okayu, thank you for today!
いつもさ、ゲストとか呼んでるけど、
I'm always inviting guests and all,
毎回予定合わせてきてくれて
but you always adjust your schedule for me.
おかゆってば私のこと好きすぎ！
Okayu, you like me way too much!
なんちゃって
Just kidding.
久しぶりに言った、このセリフ
It's been a while since I said that.
いつも私から呼んじゃってるけどさ、
I'm always the one calling you, though.
おかゆの方からもそろそろさ
It's about time you...
呼んでくれてもいいんだよ、うん、なんて…
...called me for a change. Well, I mean...
あのね、おかゆ聞いてる？
Hey, Okayu, are you listening?
おかゆ！
Okayu!
んー、あくあ、なんだって？
Hmm? Aqua, what did you say?
聞いてないんかい！
You weren't listening?!
もういいや、早く行こ！
Oh, never mind. Let's go!
あくあ、おめでとう。
Aqua, congratulations.
おかゆ〜！
Okayu~!
ちゅ、多様性。
Chu, Tayousei.
我愛你　酔いが醒めない
Wo ai ni—this buzz won't fade.
我愛你　恋が醒めない
Wo ai ni—this love won't fade.
我愛你　醒めの果てまで
Wo ai ni—until the very end of this dream.
無問題　破滅してみて
Moumantai—go ahead and ruin yourself.
褒めたい　トラウマの味
I want to praise the taste of trauma.
猛反対　お手お座りで
Against all odds, "Give me your paw," "Sit."
ハイ　報酬
Here's your reward.
なだめ空くが　ちくんちくん
Soothing the void, it's stinging.
僕ら特訓独学
We're training on our own.
断ってお得　孤独　消してみせてよ
Refuse the deal, try and make this loneliness vanish.
愛も恋も独占して
Monopolize both love and affection.
僕を独占して
Monopolize me.
このまま中毒になるまで
Until we're completely addicted...
チューしよう
...let's kiss.
そして　ゲゲゲロ　ゲゲゲロ　ゲチュー
And then, ge-ge-ge-get you.
ゲゲゲロ　ゲゲゲロ　ゲチュー
Ge-ge-ge-get you.
熱く溶けるくらいに　溢れた気持ちが
Feelings overflowing so much they might melt...
たまらないでしょ
...are irresistible, right?
ゲゲゲロ　ゲゲゲロ　ゲチュー
Ge-ge-ge-get you.
ゲゲゲロ　ゲゲゲロ　ゲチュー　ゲロゲロ
Ge-ge-ge-get you, ge-ro-ge-ro.
我愛你
Wo ai ni.
無問題
Moumantai.
ゲゲゲのチュー
Ge-ge-ge-no-kiss.
ポンチカン　勝負はいつも
Punchikan—the match is always...
ポンチカン　僕に言わせりゃ
Punchikan—if you ask me...
チンプンカン　プンだ最後は
Chinpunkan—it's a huff at the end...
L.O.でしょう
...it's Game Over.
もう何回　やられればいい
How many more times must I lose?
終わらない　忘れられない
It never ends, I can't forget.
終わらない　でときめき　変愛
In this unending, heart-pounding, strange love.
余興
Just a sideshow.
喉の奥が　ちくんちくん
Deep in my throat, it's stinging.
僕ら特訓独学
We're training on our own.
心臓ごと　引きずり出して見せてよ
Go ahead, drag out my very heart for me.
気持ちいいね　めんどくさいけど
It feels good, even if it's a bother.
やっぱ　照れくさいけど
It's still embarrassing, though.
ちゅ、多様性。
Chu, Tayousei.
芯の芯まで忘れられないちゅしよう
Let's kiss to the core of our souls, an unforgettable kiss
狂れた魂はゾンビであふれる
Crazed souls are overflowing with zombies
君は僕に恋してる
You're in love with me
ときめく胸につながるロープを惹きなよ
Pull the rope that connects to your fluttering heart
Pappaparapara Pappaparapara Chu
まじで狂える黒い脳裏うつくしさ顔
Honestly going crazy, the beauty of the black depression
美しいでしょう
It's beautiful, isn't it?
Get get get get chu
せーの、ポン・チー・カン
Ready, set, Pon, Chii, Kan
終わらない Get get get get chu
It won't end, get get get get chu
お前も愛に
You too, into love
もう無問題
No more problems
Get get get get chu
ねえ、あくあちゃん緊張してんの？
Hey, Aqua-chan, are you nervous?
あー、もう緊張してるよ
Ah, I'm already so nervous
あくあ様、リラックスリラックス
Aqua-sama, relax, relax
ほらあくあ、早く早く手出して！
Come on, Aqua, hurry, hurry, put your hand out!
みんな、いくよ！二期生エクゾディア、ファイトー！
Everyone, let's go! 2nd Generation Exodia, fight!
おー！
Oh!
喜びも...
Even joy...
悲しみも...
Even sadness...
あなたさえ...
Even you...
五等分の気持ち
Five-equal parts of feelings
一つ、作り笑い見抜かれ
One, my fake smile was seen through
二つ、あんたなんか大嫌いよ
Two, I hate you
三つ、真っ直ぐなこの気持ち気づいて
Three, realize these straightforward feelings
四つ、気がつくとだんだん
Four, gradually I realize
五つ、分かり合えたね
Five, we've come to understand each other
勉強だけじゃなくて
It's not just about studying
君を知りたいよ
I want to know about you
大嫌いから
From "I hate you"
大好きへと
to "I love you"
変わる心についていけないよ
I can't keep up with my changing heart
どんな事も
No matter what
あなたさえ
even you
五等分です
are shared in five equal parts
でも私、私、私、私、私、私は
But I, I, I, I, I, I...
あなたが好きよ
am in love with you
少し複雑に心の中
Inside my heart, it's a bit complicated
でも変わってゆく気持ち
But my feelings are changing
ずっとこんな関係続いてるいいのにな
I wish this relationship could go on forever
忘れられない思い出も
Even memories I can't forget
これから増える伝わりも
and the things I'll convey will only increase
あなたなしだったら意味がないダメよ
Without you, it would be meaningless, no way
ずっとそばで
Always by your side
教えてね
tell me, okay?
だけど勝手に胸の鼓動高鳴る
But my heart is racing all on its own
運命だって
Even if it's fate
信じられる
I can believe it
同じ気持ちで
With the same feelings
またいつか、いつか、いつか、いつか、この日も夢に見るかな
Someday, someday, someday, someday, will I dream of this day again?
少しずつ変わる想い
Feelings changing little by little
焦りや苛立ちを笑いあえてく
We can laugh together at our impatience and frustration
信じきれる自信
The confidence to believe completely
胸の奥に隠れてる言葉
The words hidden deep in my heart
甘え下手だけどいいんですかって
“I'm not good at being pampered, but is that okay?”
私ついてゆくわ
I'll follow you
いつまでも
Forever
出会えた奇跡
The miracle of us meeting
偶然じゃない、そうでしょ
It wasn't a coincidence, right?
大嫌いから
From "I hate you"
大好きへと
to "I love you"
変わる心について行きたいよ
I want to follow my changing heart
どんな事も
No matter what
あなたさえ
even you
五等分です
are shared in five equal parts
でも私、私、私、私、私、私は
But I, I, I, I, I, I...
ずっと、ずっと、ずっと、ずっとあなたに
Always, always, always, always to you
愛を誓います
I vow my love
We are the bride
Free!
あくたん、あくたん、あくあくあくたん！
Akutan, Akutan, Aku-aku-akutan!
ちょっとこの人うるさいんですけど
This person is being a little loud...
あくたん準備OK？
Akutan, are you ready?
ふふ、二人とも緊張しなさすぎ
Hehe, you two aren't nervous at all.
よし、行こうか
Alright, let's go.
No title
作詞・作曲: Reol 編曲: Giga
Lyrics/Music: Reol, Arrangement: Giga
ずっと夢見てた僕になれたかな
Did I become the person I always dreamed of?
とうに帰れないとこまで来たみたい
Seems I've come too far to return now.
自分の足で二段飛ばして
Skipping two steps at a time with my own feet,
さあもっと先へ駆けていけるはずだから runaway
I should be able to run even further, so runaway.
深くなる傷を縫い付け
Stitching up the deepening wounds,
繋ぐパッチワーク回りだす
The connecting patchwork begins to turn.
慣れた痛み 焦る呼吸とビート
Familiar pain, hurried breaths and the beat,
気付かないフリしてまた一人
Pretending not to notice, alone once again.
何が正当？ ないな永劫
What is correct? Not for eternity,
誰が間違った対価払うの
Who will pay the price for mistakes?
あんたが嫌いなあいつはきっと
That person you hate is surely...
ただ「これ」が好きで不正解なんだ
Just an incorrect answer for liking 'this'.
0点だって提言したって
Even if declared a zero-point score,
全然納得できない理由も
There's no reason I'd ever agree.
最前線はいつだってここだった
The front line was always right here.
最善策は最初からなかった
There was never a best plan from the start.
緩やかに崩れ壊れてく
Slowly collapsing and breaking apart.
ゆらりゆらり首を締めるように
Swaying as if tightening a noose,
昨日までの僕が殺されていく
The me of yesterday is being killed.
緩やかに離れ離れ飽く
Slowly drifting apart, getting tired of it.
ぐらりりき君に聞こえるのは
Wavering, what you hear
僕が知らない声になっていく
Is becoming a voice I don't recognize.
幼い頃から
Since I was young,
気付いたらそばにいた
When I realized, you were by my side.
まるで空気のようだ
Just like the very air,
僕は君とぎゅっと手を繋いで
I held your hand so tightly.
楽しいことも涙も
The happy times and the tears,
僕は君に話して聞かせた
I told you all about them.
僕を笑う人 貶す声が
So the voices that laughed and mocked me
聞こえないように君は歌った
Wouldn't be heard, you sang for me.
この声を君が受信
You receive this voice,
また夜ごと投影されてく憂い
And every night, the sorrow is projected.
使い捨てだって言って腐っても
Even if called disposable and rotting away,
止まらないハイファイ・ファイ・フィスト
The high-fi-fi-fist won't stop.
一周巡る間の
In the time it takes for one rotation,
たった一瞬だけでも
Even if for just a single moment,
交わる鼓動、音、繋ぐ色
The meeting heartbeat, sound, and connecting colors.
次は僕が君に歌うから
Because next time, I'll be the one singing to you.
緩やかに崩れ壊れてく
Slowly collapsing and breaking apart.
ゆらりゆらり首を締めるように
Swaying as if tightening a noose,
昨日までの僕が殺されていく
The me of yesterday is being killed.
緩やかに離れ離れ飽く
Slowly drifting apart, getting tired of it.
ぐらりりき君に聞こえるのは
Wavering, what you hear
僕が知らない声になっていく
Is becoming a voice I don't recognize.
緩やかに崩れ壊れてく
Slowly collapsing and breaking apart.
ゆらりゆらり首を締めるように
Swaying as if tightening a noose,
昨日までの僕が殺されていく
The me of yesterday is being killed.
緩やかに離れ離れ飽く
Slowly drifting apart, getting tired of it.
ぐらりりき君に聞こえるのは
Wavering, what you hear
僕が知らない声になっていく
Is becoming a voice I don't recognize.
いつか君に届くかな
I wonder if it'll reach you someday.
いやそんな日はきっと来ないだろうな
No, that day will surely never come.
声も体も持たぬ君に
By you, who has neither voice nor body,
救われた何億人の一人
I am just one of hundreds of millions saved.
赤青黄合わせ彩った
Combining red, blue, and yellow to color it,
音で世界が溢れた
The world overflowed with sound.
巡り巡り出会ったこの音を聴く
I listen to this sound found through twists and turns.
すべてが
Everything...
緩やかに崩れ壊れてく
Slowly collapsing and breaking apart.
ゆらりゆらり首を締めるように
Swaying as if tightening a noose,
昨日までの僕が殺されていく
The me of yesterday is being killed.
緩やかに離れ離れ飽く
Slowly drifting apart, getting tired of it.
ぐらりりき君に聞こえるのは
Wavering, what you hear
僕が知らない声になっていく
Is becoming a voice I don't recognize.
緩やかに崩れ壊れてく
Slowly collapsing and breaking apart.
ゆらりゆらり首を締めるように
Swaying as if tightening a noose,
昨日までの僕が殺されていく
The me of yesterday is being killed.
緩やかに離れ離れ飽く
Slowly drifting apart, getting tired of it.
ぐらりりき君に聞こえるのは
Wavering, what you hear
僕が知らない声になっていく
Is becoming a voice I don't recognize.
社長ー！
Boss!
ってそっか、もう社長じゃないんだった。
Oh, that's right. You're not the boss anymore.
先行ってますからね！
We're going on ahead!
もうあくきん遅すぎて、マリンおばあちゃんになっちゃうんだわ。
Akukin is taking so long,
I'm going to turn into Grandma Marine.
一番の宝物 〜Yui final ver.〜
My Most Precious Treasure ~Yui final ver.~
作詞・作曲 麻枝准
Lyrics/Composition: Jun Maeda
顔を合わせたら
Whenever we'd see each other,
喧嘩してばかり
we'd do nothing but bicker.
それもいい思い出だった
Even that was a good memory.
君が教えてくれたんだ
You're the one who taught me
もう怖くない
I don't have to be afraid anymore.
どんな不自由でも
No matter what hardships come,
幸せを掴める
I can find happiness.
だから
And so...
独りでもゆくよ
I'll keep going, even alone,
例え辛くても
even if it's painful.
君と見た夢は
The dream I shared with you,
必ず持っていくよ
I'll always carry it with me.
君とがよかった
I'm glad it was with you,
ほかの誰でもない
and no one else.
でも目覚めた朝
But when I woke up this morning,
君は居ないんだね
you weren't there, were you?
ずっと遊んでられる
We could play forever,
そんな気がしてた
that's how it felt.
気がしていただけ
It was just a feeling,
分かってる
I know that.
生まれてきたことも後悔はしない
I won't regret being born into this world.
祭りの後みたい寂しいけど
It's lonely, like the end of a festival,
そろそろ行こう
but it's time to go.
どこまでもゆくよ
I'll go anywhere,
ここで知ったこと
everything I learned here,
幸せという夢を
the dream called "happiness",
叶えてみせるよ
I'll make it come true.
君と離れても
Even if we're apart,
どんなに遠くなっても
no matter how far we are,
新しい朝に
in the new morning,
あたしは生きるよ
I will live on.
独りでもゆくよ
I'll keep going, even alone,
死にたくなっても
even if I want to die.
声が聞こえるよ
I can hear your voice,
死んではいけないと
telling me I mustn't die.
例え辛くても
Even if it's painful,
寂しさに泣いても
even if I cry from loneliness,
心の奥には温もりを感じるよ
I feel your warmth deep within my heart.
巡って流れて時は移ろいだ
Time flows on in cycles, changing as it goes.
もう何があったか思い出せないけど
I can't remember what happened anymore,
目を閉じてみれば
but if I close my eyes...
誰かの笑い声
...I hear someone's laughter.
いくべ
Let's go!
なぜかそれが今
For some reason, right now,
一番の宝物
it's my most precious treasure.
あくたんも、社員だったみんな、
Akutan, and everyone who was an employee,
あくきん建設を楽しんでくれた、世界中の人へ。
to all the people worldwide who enjoyed Akukin Construction.
ありがとう。
Thank you.
あくあ先輩、待ちくたびれたぺこよ。
Aqua-senpai, I've been waiting for ages-peko.
ぺこらちゃん。
Pekora-chan.
ごめん、待っててくれてありがとう。
Sorry. Thank you for waiting for me.
いつもモノクロだった瞳の奥の",
Deep in my eyes that were always monochrome,
景色捨てたら夢見つけた
I found a dream once I cast the scenery away.
何もない世界で創る絆は
The bonds we create in a world with nothing
強い意志与えた
gave me a strong will.
裏返した日常でもまた
Even in an upended daily life, once again,
走って行く先に君はいた
you were there at the end of where I ran.
触れた心は輝いた
The heart I touched sparkled.
鮮やかな色になって羽ばたくよ希望のせて
Turning into vivid colors, I'll spread my wings, carrying hope.
無限に広がる空の下詰まった
Under the infinitely spreading sky, the
願い守り進めばまた
wishes I've gathered, if I protect them and move on,
まだ誰も知らない明日へと
towards a tomorrow that no one knows yet.
引き寄せられるように覗いた瞬間
The moment I peeked in as if being drawn,
光の糸は君包んだ
a thread of light wrapped around you.
細く千切れそうな絡まった運命
An entangled fate that seems thin and about to break,
きっとまだ変われる
I'm sure it can still change.
間違えても信じた道は
Even if I make a mistake, the path I believed in
新しい景色を照らすだろう
will likely illuminate a new scenery.
巡る時の中笑って
Laughing as time goes around,
様々な想い持って始めようまた一から
with various feelings, let's start again from scratch.
辿り着いた儚き奇跡壊れないように
So that the fleeting miracle I reached doesn't break,
手を伸ばし繋げばほら
look, if I reach out my hand and connect,
君はそばでいつまでも
you'll be by my side forever.
まだ透明な私たちはどんな色にでも
We, who are still transparent, can turn into any color.
染まることが出来るから夢叶えよう
Because we can be stained, let's make our dreams come true
ずっと独りぼっちだった
I was always all alone.
孤独だった
I was lonely.
寂しかった
I was sad.
でも今は独りじゃない
But now, I'm not alone.
大切な仲間たちがいる
I have precious friends.
応援してくれてるファンの皆がいる
I have all the fans who support me.
昔の私 もう大丈夫だよ
To the me of the past... it's okay now.
私はもう独りじゃない
I'm not alone anymore.
だから 大丈夫
So, it's okay.
銀河一アイドル 湊あくあ
The galaxy's number one idol, Minato Aqua.
世界中 あくあ色に染まれ！
Let the whole world be stained in Aqua's color!
何をしてもしどろもどろで
No matter what I do, I'm flustered...
何かとミスしてばっか
...and I keep making mistakes.
ダメダメな私だって
Even for a useless me like this...
出来ることがあるの
...there are things I can do.
凹んで悲しくたって
Even if I'm feeling down and sad...
笑顔にしてあげるんだ
...I'll make you smile.
ここにいるから早く
I'm right here, so hurry up...
私を見つけてね
...and find me.
いつでも隣にいるし
I'll always be by your side...
いつでも一緒に笑える
...and we can always laugh together.
私をたくさん知って
Get to know me a lot...
たくさん好きって言って
...and say you like me a lot.
わがままで朝も苦手
I'm selfish and not a morning person...
ドジだしダメダメだけど
...I'm clumsy and useless, but...
それでも私のことを
Even so, please keep...
見ててね
...looking at me.
描く夢の未来へ
Toward the future of the dreams I draw...
続く道は
...the path that continues...
君と歩めますように
...I hope to walk it with you.
ねえ もっと好きになってもらいたいんだ
Hey, I want you to like me even more.
頭の中は君ばっかって
My head is filled only with you...
嘘なんてついてないで
...don't lie like that.
あぁ もやもやしちゃうわ あぁ
Ah, I'm getting all restless, ah!
ずっとずっと好きでいろ！
Keep liking me forever and ever!
心の奥まで入れちゃうくらいに
So much that I get deep into your heart.
こっち向いててよね ダーリン
Keep facing this way, darling.
あぁ 離さないから絶対に
Ah, because I'll never let you go!
君がいるから私
Because you are here...
いつでも頑張れるんだ
...I can always do my best.
落ち込んで悲しくたって
Even if I'm feeling down and sad...
君がいるから！
...it's because you are here!
みんなのおかげでここまで来ることが出来たよ！
Thanks to everyone, I was able to come this far!
いきました！
Here we go!
6年目もみんなアクア色に染まれ！
May everyone be dyed in Aqua's color in my 6th year!
君がいるから 歩いてこれた
Because you're here, I've been able to walk this path
君がいなくちゃ 前も見れない
Without you, I couldn't even see what's ahead
嫌なこととか 辛いこととかあったって
Even when there were bad things or painful things
君の力で ここまで笑ってこれたんだ
With your strength, I was able to keep smiling
今度はもっと 私がグッと引っ張って
This time, I'll pull you along much harder
連れていくんだ
I'll take you with me
君がいるから 私がいるの
I exist because you are here
こんな私を 愛してくれるね
You'll love me for who I am, right?
もっと もっと
More, more
まだもっと 受け止めてよね
Accept even more of me, okay?
ねぇいい？
Hey, is it okay?
さあ声を上げて
Now, raise your voices!
好きになってもらいたいわ
I want you to fall in love with me
いつでもそう 私ばかり見て
Always look only at me like that
欲張りなんて 言わせないわ
I won't let you call me greedy
ねほら夢中にしちゃうわ ああ
See, I'll make you crazy about me, ah
ずっとずっと好きだよ
I'll love you forever and ever
心も体も染まっちゃうくらいに
So much that your heart and body are dyed
こっち向いててよね ダーリン もう離さないから
Keep looking this way, darling, I won't let go now
絶対に
Never
絶対ね
Promise me
絶対よ
I mean it
約束だよー！
It's a promise!
愛しちゃうもっと
I'll love you even more
ありがとうございましたー！
Thank you so much!
ということで、ここまでノンストップでお届けしてきました、
And so, we've delivered non-stop up to this point,
湊あくあ5周年ライブ、みんなどうだった！？
Minato Aqua's 5th-anniversary live, how was it, everyone!?
ありがとうー。
Thank you.
ということでね、えー、皆様のおかげで
And well, thanks to all of you,
無事5周年を迎えることができました！
I've safely reached my 5th anniversary!
みんな本当にありがとうございます！
Thank you so much, everyone!
ありがとうー。
Thank you.
ということで、ちょっとコメントもたくさん、ありがとう。
Also, thank you for all the comments.
はーぱちぱちありがとうございます. 最高だった？
Yeah, clap clap, thank you. Was it the best?
本当に？ありがとう、嬉しい。
Really? Thank you, I'm happy.
いやなんとね、もうここまでゲストさんもたくさん来てくれて、
And wow, so many guests have come so far.
いやーどうですか？エモかったですか？
Well, how was it? Was it emotional?
ちょっとね、あの私がみんなに込めた思い、そして
This is a live performance I've created with many of the thoughts I've put into all of you,
みんなに届けたい気持ちをたくさん込めて作ったライブでございます。
and the feelings I want to deliver to everyone.
みんな本当にね、見てくれてありがとう！
Thank you so much for watching, everyone!
なんと！なんとトレンドが1位になった！
What!? We reached #1 on trends!
すごーい！ありがとう！
Amazing! Thank you!
ヤゴー水着配信ぶりだ(笑) ありがとうございまーす。
It's the first time since Yagoo's swimsuit stream (laughs). Thank you very much.
いや嬉しいです、いやここまでね、来れたのも本当にみんなのおかげだと思ってます。
I'm so happy. I believe I've been able to come this far thanks to all of you.
6年目もよろしくお願いします！
Please continue to support me in my 6th year!
ありがとねー。
Thank you!
あ、まだね、続くからね、まだ続きますから。
Oh, it's not over yet, it's still continuing.
そして、なんと今回はですね、
And, actually, this time,
私の5周年をお祝いしてメッセージを
someone has sent a message
送ってくださってる方がいらっしゃるみたいなので、
to celebrate my 5th anniversary,
いやーちょっと私もちょっと中身をまだ見ていなくて、
so... I haven't seen the content yet,
ちょっと楽しみなんだよね。
so I'm really looking forward to it.
それでは早速VTR、どうぞ！
Well then, without further ado, let's watch the VTR!
こんにちは、ホロライブスタッフの友人Aです。
Hello, I'm Hololive staff's Friend A.
あくあさん、5周年おめでとうございます！
Aqua-san, congratulations on your 5th anniversary!
最初に会ってからもう5周年が、
I'm a bit surprised that 5 years,
5年が経過していることにちょっとびっくりですけれども、
already 5 years have passed since we first met,
まああくあさんは最初ね、会ったときからちっちゃいながらもすごい可愛くて、
but well, ever since we first met, you've been small but very cute,
クルーの皆さんのことも思って、うん、
always thinking of the crew, and,
そして歌もダンスも頑張っていて、がんばりやなアイドルの印象がとってもあります。
working hard at singing and dancing, giving the impression of a hard-working idol.
もうね、色々なホロメンもね、あの可愛がってもらっているなというイメージがありますし、
I also have the impression that you're well-loved by many Hololive members,
なんか色んなところも成長、成長を感じる(？)
and I feel your growth in various ways...
(私を差し置いて)
(Leaving me behind)
Aちゃん！全然成長してない！
A-chan! I haven't grown at all!
ゲームもね、すごい上り詰めて頑張るというところをいつも応援しておりますが、
I've always been supporting you as you climb to the top and work hard in games, but
一点、あくあさんを見ていてすごく気づきがあったと言うか、
there's one point where I've had a realization, or rather,
学びがありました。あの...
a lesson from watching Aqua-san. That is...
色々ところか成長していても
Even though you've grown in many ways...
意外とコミュ力って伸びないんですねｗ
...it's surprising how your communication skills haven't improved. (lol)
それでは また バイバイ
Well then, bye-bye!
今度は直接煽らせてくださいな
Let me tease you in person next time.
ははは、じゃないよ 何これ
Ha ha ha... no way, what is this!
なんか芸能人かなんかからのさメッセージかと思ったら Aちゃん！？
I thought it was a message from some celebrity, but it's A-chan!?
ありがとうAちゃん ありがとうこざいます
Thank you, A-chan! Thank you very much!
いや まあ5周年にふさわしい相手ではこざいましたけど
Well, she was an appropriate person for the 5th anniversary, but...
なんか、え、何、Aちゃん、なんか嫉妬してんの？私の成長っぷりに！
Wait, what? A-chan, are you jealous? Of how much I've grown!
本当に全く 最近丸くなったAちゃんなんですけど、ちょっと何が若干尖ってたな
Seriously. A-chan's been mellowing out lately, but she was a bit sharp just now.
許せねえな あいつ許せねえな マジで
Unforgivable. I can't forgive her, seriously.
え、なんと！もう一人メッセージをくれた人がいるみたいです！
Eh? No way! It looks like there's one more person who sent a message!
ちょ、やっぱりこれAちゃんは前座だった？もしや。いやいやそんなことありがとうございます
Wait, was A-chan just the opening act? Maybe. No, no, thank you anyway!
誰だ？大物らしいぞ！すごい大物からのメッセージが届いてるみたいです！
Who is it? It seems like someone big! A message from someone really important has arrived!
それでは VTRどうぞ
Well then, here's the VTR!
自己紹介をお願いします！
Please introduce yourself!
カバー株式会社代表の谷郷元昭です。よろしくお願いします。
I'm Motoaki Tanigo, CEO of Cover Corp. Nice to meet you.
待って... 待って、え？
Wait... wait, eh?
あくあさんへ5周年のメッセージをお願いします！
Please give a message to Aqua-san for her 5th anniversary!
あくあさん 5周年おめてとうこざいます
Aqua-san, congratulations on your 5th anniversary.
5周年って本当に素晴らしいですよね。本当に今まで、あの、頑張っていただいてありがとうございます。
5 years is truly wonderful. Thank you so much for all your hard work up until now.
いや こちらこそありがとうございます
No, the thanks are mine.
あくあさんとの思い出を聞かせてください！
Please tell us about your memories with Aqua-san!
何この間！この間は何だよ！
What's with this pause! What's this pause for!
あくあさんとの思い出ですが あくあさん あの二期生の中で あの 一人単独のオーディションだったので
My memory with Aqua-san is... among the 2nd generation, Aqua-san had a solo audition...
どういった方が来るのかなっていうふうに思っていた中で あの お会いして まさにこの人があくあさんだなと思ったことを覚えています
While I was wondering what kind of person would come, I remember meeting her and thinking, "This person is definitely Aqua-san."
本当かよ！本当に？嬉しいな
Is that true? Really? I'm happy.
締めの挨拶をお願いします！
Please give a closing greeting!
だからこの間何だよ！この間は何だよ！
I'm telling you, what's with this pause! What's this pause for!
5周年っていうことて
Since it's your 5th anniversary...
台本読んでる！
He's reading a script!
これからも 配信たけでなく
...I hope we can continue to work hard...
この顔何だよ！この顔は何だよ！誰だよこれ 何だよ！
What's with this face! What's this face for! Who even is this, what is it!
ありがとうございました
Thank you very much.
ありがとうございました！
Thank you very much!
何、何の魔がさ... 魔がさ、すごい何、台本読んでるでしょ！
What... what possessed him... he was totally reading from a script!
YAGOOからのメッセージでした。ありがとうございました。何あれ、なんか...
That was a message from YAGOO. Thank you very much. What was that...
なんか加工強っｗ 今時のJKってあんな感じなの？やっぱり
The filter is so strong lol. Is that what modern high school girls are like?
あのすごい もう世界一のアイドルともなると あんな あんな感じなんだ すごい血色もやばかったけど 顔色悪くない？大丈夫？ちゃんと寝てる？
When you become the world's number one idol, that's what it's like. His complexion was crazy, but doesn't he look pale? Is he okay? Is he sleeping properly?
ありがとうこざいます！やばい ちょっと笑いすきて やばい 歌えるかな この次も
Thank you very much! Oh no, I'm laughing too much, I wonder if I can sing the next song.
またね な 次もありますから。改めてお二人ともありがとうこざいました！ありがとう！ありがとね！
Well, there's more to come. Once again, thank you to both of you! Thank you! Thanks!
すごい マジでなんかネタみたいなメッセージをいたたきました。ありがとうこざいました
That was amazing, I received some messages that felt like comedy skits. Thank you very much.
改めてね 皆様ね スタッフの皆さんも ホロメンも そしてここにいるみんな 本当にここまでありがとうこざいました これからもよろしくお願いします
Once again, everyone, the staff, the Hololive members, and everyone here, thank you so much for everything up to now. I look forward to your continued support.
あ、そうた。そう。ちょっとたけ告知していい？
Ah, that's right. Yes. Can I make a small announcement?
え、クッズの方をチェック皆様もうしましたか？なんとね 8月の8日に発売されたクッズかあります じゃあ ちょっと出ますかね？こちら トン！
Um, have you all checked out the merchandise yet? There's merchandise that was released on August 8th. Well, can we see it? Here it is, bam!
活動5周年記念フルセット！こちらね もう販売されておりまスケとも 今も概要欄て買えますのて もしね 今からても気になった方はぜひぜひチェックしてみてね
5th Anniversary Memorial Full Set! It's already on sale, and you can still buy it from the description box, so if you're interested even now, please check it out.
何かあるかというと トン！こちら！
As for what's included... bam! Here!
B2タペストリー！可愛いね！ふわり先生に描き下ろしていたたいた これね あの準備してる私てす 今から出かけるそっていう私てす そしてこちら！
B2 Tapestry! So cute! Illustrated by Fuwari-sensei, this is me getting ready. This is me about to head out. And here!
陰キャ証明書！これね めっちゃ売れてるらしいｗ これなんかね めっちゃ売れてるという情報を入手しました 何てたよ！何てたよ！みんな みんな陰キャ証明書欲しい？いや ありがとうこざいます そしてこちら！トトン！
Introvert Certificate! Apparently, this is selling like crazy lol. I've received information that it's selling really well. Why!? Why!? Does everyone want an Introvert Certificate? Well, thank you. And here! Ta-da!
あくたんと一緒にお出かけリュックサック！これね すっとリュック私欲しくて ちょっと一緒にお出かけしませんか？私もちょっとお出かけする時にリュック持ちたいなーなんて 結構可愛いてす そしてこちら！テテン！もうサクサク行っちゃうからね
Backpack for Outings with Akutan! I've always wanted a backpack, so won't you go out with me? I also wanted a backpack to carry when I go out. It's quite cute. And here! Ta-da! I'm going through these quickly.
あくたんとおそろいネックレス！これね あの制服衣装て私か付けてるネックレスとなんと お揃いのネックレスてす これネックレスにもなるし チャームにもなるのてせひこちらもチェックしてくたさい これもなんか売れてるらしいそ そして トトン！
Matching Necklace with Akutan! This is actually the same necklace that I wear with my school uniform outfit. You can use it as a necklace or a charm, so please check this out too. Apparently, this is selling well too. And, ta-da!
はい これ全部買ったら え サインか付きます というフルセットてす なのて皆様また また買ってない人 買ってね！時間ね あの 期限あるから買ってね よろしくお願いします！
Yes, if you buy everything, it comes with an autograph. That's the full set. So those of you who haven't bought it yet, please do! There's a deadline, so please buy it. Thank you!
はい ということて そして やはい 告知かたくさん そしてなんとてすね この後21時15分より メンバーシップ限定て アンコールライブを行いたいと思います！アンコールてす！
Alright, and oh boy, so many announcements. And believe it or not, from 21:15 onwards, I'll be holding an encore live performance exclusively for members! It's an encore!
はい ちゃんとね あのこのステーシてなんと 歌うらしい ということて ミニライブかありますのて
Yes, apparently I'll be singing on this very stage. So, there will be a mini-live...
ぜひみんなメンバーシップに入ってね
Everyone, please join the membership.
なんかめっちゃでもメンバー増えてる気がするんだよね
I feel like the number of members is really increasing, though.
ありがとうございます
Thank you very much.
ぜひみんなメンバー入ってくれたら嬉しいです
I'd be happy if everyone joined.
メン限よろしくお願いします
Please look forward to member-only content.
そして
And then...
えー、えー、次が最後の曲となるんですが
Um, the next song will be the last one...
えー、ライブで歌うのは
...but as for singing it live...
初めてのオリジナル曲になっております
...this is the first time for this original song.
こちらです。デデン！
Here it is. Ta-da!
君の最推しにしてよ！
Minato Aqua
作詞 作曲 HoneyWorks
Make Me Your Number One!
Minato Aqua
Lyrics/Composition by HoneyWorks
君の最推しにしてよ！
Make Me Your Number One!
こちらね、なんか誕生日かなんかに実はあのもう
This one, actually on my birthday or something...
あの配信は開始されてはいたんですけども
...the distribution had already started, but...
はい、こちらHoneyWorksさんが書き下ろしてくださいました
Yes, this one was written for me by HoneyWorks.
「君の最推しにしてよ！」のMVがなんと
The MV for 'Make Me Your Number One!' will...
このあと21時5分よりプレミア公開となります
...premiere at 21:05 after this!
これねMVなんとですね、HoneyWorksさんがプロデュースして
The MV was actually produced by HoneyWorks...
作ってくださいました！すごーい！
...and they made it! Amazing!
なのでぜひね、MVも見に
So please go watch the MV...
そして曲を知らない方はぜひチェックしてください
...and for those who don't know the song, please check it out.
ぜひぜひって言いすぎたな。コホン。
I said 'please' too many times. *Cough*
それでは！
And now!
この曲聴いていただきたいとおもいます
I'd like you to listen to this song.
最後の曲です
The last song.
君の最推しにしてよ！
Make Me Your Number One!
ハートをくれた分だけ
For every heart you gave me
私は君に恋する
I'll fall in love with you
ハートをくれた分だけ
For every heart you gave me
私は夢を叶える
I'll make my dreams come true
ねぇ愛して？
Hey, love me?
愛して！
Love me!
ハイ！
Hi!
一緒にいこう
Let's go together
頂上
To the top
目指す
Aiming for it
我が民よ！あくたん！
My people! Akutan!
憧れのアイドル目指して
Aiming to be the idol of my dreams
配信レッスン忙しいです
I'm busy with streaming and lessons
疲れてる時に見てしまった
I saw it when I was tired
アンチコメントに落ち込む
Getting depressed over anti-comments
「才能無い」「努力は無駄」「辞めろ」とか
'No talent', 'Effort is wasted', 'Just quit'
そうかって呑まれそうな時もある
There are times I'm about to be swallowed by such thoughts
大嫌い 大嫌い
I hate it, I hate it
弱虫ハート
My cowardly heart
もっと強くなるために君の最推しにしてよ！
Make me your number one so I can become stronger!
ハートをくれた分だけ私は君に恋する
For every heart you gave me, I'll fall in love with you
くれた分だけ私は夢を叶える
For every heart you gave, I'll make my dreams come true
ねぇ愛して？
Hey, love me?
愛して！
Love me!
ハイ！一緒にいこう
Hi! Let's go together
ハイ！
Hi!
頂上目指す
Aiming for the top
我が民よ！あくたん！
My people! Akutan!
分かればよろしい！
As long as you understand!
応援してくれてる君に
To you who is supporting me
ありがとオムライス
Thank you omurice
元気出ない時会いに来て
Come see me when you're feeling down
絶対笑顔にさせるから！
Because I'll definitely make you smile!
「実力無い」「トップは無理」「消えろ」とか
'No ability', 'Top is impossible', 'Disappear'
そうかって挫けそうな時もある
There are times I'm about to break down
大嫌い 大嫌い
I hate it, I hate it
ネガティブ私
The negative me
もっと強くなるために君の最推しにしてよ！
Make me your number one so I can become stronger!
推しマが増えた分だけ私は君に恋する
For every 'oshi mark' added, I'll fall in love with you
増えた分だけ私は夢中になれる
For every one added, I can become more obsessed
ねぇ どうしよう？
Hey, what should I do?
どうしよう！かなっちゃうかも
What should I do! It might come true
夢を追いかけ
Chasing the dream
我が民よ！あくたん！
My people! Akutan!
振り返れば最初は泣いてばかりだったっけ
Looking back, at first I was just crying, wasn't I?
もう大丈夫
I'm okay now
いつもありがとね
Thank you always
もう大丈夫
I'm okay now
君が隣にいてくれる
Because you are by my side
もう大丈夫
I'm okay now
君が愛してくれる
Because you love me
君が名前を呼んでくれる
Because you call my name
君の酸素は？
Your oxygen is?
君の血肉は？
Your flesh and blood is?
君の女神は？
Your goddess is?
今日の主役は？
Today's star is?
あくたん！
Akutan!
辞めろとか
Stop it, or...
...そうかもって
...maybe that's true,
飲まれそうな時もある
there are times when I feel overwhelmed.
大嫌い 大嫌い
I hate it, I hate it,
弱虫ハート
my cowardly heart.
もっと強くなるために
To become even stronger,
君の最推しにしてよ！
make me your number one!
ハートをくれた分だけ 私は
Just as much as the heart you gave me,
君に恋する
I'll fall in love with you.
くれた分だけ 私は
Just as much as you gave me,
夢を叶える
I'll make your dreams come true.
ねぇ愛して？
Hey, love me?
ハイ！
Yes!
一緒にいこう？
Let's go together?
ハイ！
Yes!
頂点目指す
Aiming for the top!
ハイ！
Yes!
我が民よ！
My people!
分かればよろしい！
That's good to hear!
Yeah!
おしまい
The end.
湊あくあ5周年記念Live Dreamy day
Minato Aqua 5th Anniversary Live: Dreamy day